WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
I'm more of a dog man myself,
but no cat deserves this.
Did you tell anyone
about why you were down here?
Someone on the plane?
Someone you met at a restaurant?
'Course not.
Not to get personal,
but have you had any, uh... encounters?
_
Murphy, join t' party, huh?
- "Encounters"?
- Yeah.
I'm married.
Right.
What's wrong?
_
Only people I've encountered
outside the DEA and my wife
All you guys having a good time?
You gotta let it go, man.
There's good that came out of this.
are those Colombian cops in Medellín.
No, no, Carrillo's solid.
Yeah, we used him,
then we got him killed.
_
Did anyone have access
to your credentials?
Did you drop your wallet?
No, we didn't kill him... Escobar did.
Passport.
And now we get to go after
that motherfucker.
Nowadays, the US
government can listen to anything you say.
How important is this cat to you?
Look on the bright side, huh?
Excuse me?
They know where you are,
they know who you're talking to,
You gave someone your passport?
Peña was right.
There was a silver lining.
and trust me,
they know who you're fucking.
We were trying to get Puff
through Immigration.
"Puff"?
One of the sicarios caught
after Lara Bonilla's assassination
You turn on a cell phone or a computer,
and you're doomed.
I didn't name it, dude.
Traffickers pay people
at the airports for intel.
confessed that Pablo had put out the hit.
But in Colombia in 1989,
it wasn't that easy.
A gringo coming in from Miami raises
suspicions. That's how you got made.
An important politician had been murdered
and everyone knew who did it.
First off,
there was no Internet.
Don't let it rattle you.
That's what they want.
You probably got a price on your head,
but no one's gonna take the contract.
No cells.
The best they had were satellite phones,
Fucking price on my head?
Finally, the Colombian government
had to react.
and in order to capture a satellite phone,
you had to fly directly over it.
There's a standing bounty
of 350,000 US on any DEA down here,
Pablo Escobar was indicted
for the murder of Rodrigo Lara Bonilla.
On top of that, the only people
who had sat phones were the filthy rich...
but you're safe... because of Kiki.
WANTED: PABLO ESCOBAR GAVIRIA
$100,000 REWARD
Colombia agreed to the one thing
narcos feared most: extradition.
the landowners, the politicians...
The "Kiki" Peña was referring to
was Kiki Camarena, a DEA agent who went
after the Guadalajara cartel in Mexico.
And lucky for us,
the narcos were richer than them all.
Now any Colombian
who smuggled drugs to America
Kiki was captured and tortured.
could be prosecuted
and jailed in the US,
They skinned his legs,
put a bullet in each limb,
even if they never
stepped foot on our soil.
What's up, Lizard?
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.MY-SUBS.com
used an electric drill on his head
until he died.
This made all the difference in the world.
We're going out tonight.
If you were a narco in Colombia,
What the fuck were they thinking?
They could kill an American
government agent and get away with it?
jail time meant banging girls,
watching movies,
And once you got a signal,
you didn't know who you were listening to.
By the time I left Miami,
hanging with the fellas...
Americans were doing a couple hundred tons
of cocaine every year.
Uncle Sam doesn't fuck around.
The cocksuckers paid in blood.
Grease the right hands and you'd
get a reduced sentence for good behavior.
That's why back then, the US government
developed software that could identify
the voices of our targets.
To satisfy American noses,
the narcos ramped up their operations.
They went after them so hard,
every single narco in the world
It was a fucking joke.
Back home,
it was a whole different deal.
I got Poison at 400 to 1700 megahertz,
gentlemen.
got the message
that the DEA is off-limits.
The seventh richest man in the world?
No one gives a shit.
And you guessed it:
no GPS either.
- Here, honey.
- Ah, thank you.
Kiki was like Jesus Christ to us.
You still get a 6x8 cell 23 hours a day,
just like every other loser,
He died to save us all.
Hammer, prepare to engage.
- Hey, is that the Bahamas?
- Hm?
Do not tell Connie that story.
Once we got a target,
we still had to locate it.
a fucking nightmare.
Oh... Yeah.
I won't.
- But you shouldn't forget it either.
- Why?
Now Pablo had someone to fear: us.
So we had to triangulate their signals
using assets on the ground.
That's beautiful.
This cat is DEA.
They were flying so many planes,
Mark my words, it will get justice.
OK, he's in Modelia.
He's on the west side.
they needed a refueling stop
between Colombia and Miami.
Hawkeye, how do you copy that?
So Carlos Lehder
bought an island in the Bahamas
Can you be more specific?
Police units are standing by.
as a transshipment point
for the drugs and money.
La Dispensaria.
Turns out...
it was a damn good place to party.
I've got a table ready.
Show up around midnight.
It was modern day Sodom and Gomorrah,
with the three things Carlos liked most:
- It's gonna be raining women.
- Poison didn't know it,
but he'd just made himself a date.
- sex, drugs, and Nazi sympathizers.
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Negative on Hammer. This fuckwad
just told us where he's going.
Let's get down!
Hammer, disengage.
So who do we give this to? DEA?
- Yeah. Let's give it to Javier Peña.
- Peña's an asshole.
The problem was
no longer demand... it was supply.
- I'm gonna give it to the other guy.
- Sure.
By "the other guy," he meant me.
I'm Steve Murphy,
Drug Enforcement Agent.
We should be over the Amazon by now.
And as you can see,
I am deeply embedded in Colombia.
From 10,000 feet, Colombia
was a paradise of untouched rainforest.
Hello?
Poison will be partying
at La Dispensaria.
Got it.
But things were different
on the ground.
He's meeting Lizard
and the rest of them at midnight tonight.
OK.
Pablo and his partners built superlabs
the size of small cities.
I would've loved
to go after Poison myself,
but the DEA is restricted
in a foreign country.
From leaf to paste to powder,
they produced 10,000 kilos a week.
So I did just what you would do...
I called the cops.
Hola.
La Dispensaria?
At 50 grand a kilo,
that's five billion dollars a year.
All right.
These guys weren't fuckin' around.
Guess who that was.
Your partner.
Pablo's cousin Gustavo flew chemists in
from Germany to liquefy the cocaine.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.MY-SUBS.com
He just gave me a great gift.
Poison.
They added it to liquor, to coffee,
and just to be funny...
Extradition doesn't mean anything
unless you can catch him.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.MY-SUBS.com
- With our help, you will.
- Oh, that's right.
Does he know
how I'm going to package it?
they put it back in Coca-Cola.
¿Patrón?
Gringos to the rescue.
Yeah, sure.
Looks good?
It's one fucking man
against the United States of America.
He's not a fool.
Cocaine was no longer
hidden alongside products.
This is going
to sell better than the original.
Gotta go.
It was the product.
One man with helicopters, airplanes,
vehicles, planned escape routes,
Gonna stick me with the bill?
It's time to take Pablo's money.
- and a network of informants.
- Our government will provide money,
The narcos even
had their own drug-sniffing dogs.
My name is everywhere.
- men, weapons...
- You make it sound so easy.
Cheap son of a bitch.
Gacha bet Pablo that not even
a German scientist could fool his dog.
But Escobar has always
managed to stay one step ahead of us.
In case you're wondering,
this is the asshole.
Newspapers...
Search.
Javier Peña, my partner.
What's happening? Look at that.
magazines...
Help us catch him.
And this is Colonel Carrillo,
the leader of the Search Bloc,
I'll never be assigned to this.
Jaramillo hates my guts.
Let me take care of that.
the unit we helped create
to capture the bad guys.
Your prize dog didn't even stop.
Everyone is talking about
the "Paisa Robin Hood."
Boy, did he have
a lot of love for the narcos.
There's no coke in that boat.
- You think extradition's a victory.
- It is.
Come here.
Pablito, I'm sorry.
If I had known that--
You're going to have
to pay for that, my love.
It's blended
right into the fiberglass hull.
Party time in Zona Rosa.
Everybody goes there.
Anything you want, Pablito.
Give me the money...
the cash!
Anything I want?
Escobar will not go lightly.
Especially the local hitmen.
Yes, my love,
whatever you want.
Colombians call them sicarios.
Looks like you got taken
with this dog, brother.
You sure?
- What's up, son?
- Hey, brother.
Uh-huh.
He will make Colombia bleed.
- Hold this a moment.
- Oh, Marquessa, my dear...
Let's go inside and have a good time.
Now more than ever
is the time for solidarity.
Now, Poison, he was one of the best.
It's OK, it's OK.
Crazy motherfucker
who killed dozens of people.
You make the mistakes,
and then you preach solidarity?
Probably hundreds.
- Are you fucking crazy?
- What?
- Shut up, fag.
- What the fuck, Carlos?
But don't get me wrong.
I would've sent Carrillo there
even if Poison never killed a fly.
It's my dog.
Why are you always defending him?
Then...
Did he get your sister back
for you or not?
I don't have a lot of love
for the narcos either.
We rescued her because we did it together.
Right?
you're going to help me
get into Congress.
Son of a bitch.
What happened?
You want to know what happened? Go look.
Yes, Pablo.
It's on, boys!
Gentlemen...
We're gonna stop on 14th
and go around the corner.
Pablo?
Yes.
- Pablo, we have a motherfucking problem.
- Bastard murderer.
I suggest we form another organization
Riano, Trujillo,
you're in the front with me.
to fight against
the injustice of extradition.
- Galvis and Silva, you take up the rear.
- Yes, sir.
- He killed the dog.
- I don't give a shit.
You got it, boys? We're gonna
go at it with everything we got.
If we don't resolve this problem,
we're all dead. Come on.
Like John Lennon said,
We're gonna kill these fuckers,
all right?
- "Come together, brothers and sisters..."
- Stop that fag shit right now.
Yes, sir!
- Come on, man.
- Son of a bitch.
Those shitty oligarchs.
So Jorge...
Those people,
all of their lives...
what will we call it?
Let's see...
First, "Death to Kidnappers,"
then "the Extraditables."
don't know what it's like to wonder
where their next meal is coming from.
This is the problem?
Once again, the narcos were united
against a common enemy: jail in America.
People are watching us, Pablo.
I wouldn't blame you if you
held me responsible for this bloodbath.
They're asking themselves
how two small businessmen
I come from nothing, Valeria...
But it was not quite like
"one for all, and all for one."
- suddenly came up with so much cash.
- Gustavo, brother...
and I have more money
than any of those sons of bitches.
Yeah, I pushed the buttons.
just launder the money.
If you run for Congress, you put yourself
in the public eye, you become a target.
It was more like each man for himself.
Next!
Make it look legitimate...
that's all.
Gacha, being Gacha, decided that
all he had to do to defeat extradition
"I made my money from taxis" isn't going
to work when you face the press.
- was kill anyone who tried to arrest him.
- Fire!
Isn't that what Al Capone did?
Pablo, you need a party that supports you.
So he hired a bunch of
Israeli mercenaries and prepared for war.
But don't call me a bad guy just yet.
- Al Capone?
- Al Capone.
You need a proper political campaign.
Next!
Lehder, being Lehder, got high as a kite
and took to the airwaves.
You're a dumbass, Pablo.
I buy the press, my love.
- Al Capone is a terrible example.
- Why?
The gringos
are the ones who use the drugs.
Because Al Capone
never had this much cash.
And as far as a political party,
I am quite sure
that I can buy one of those as well.
So why are we the ones
who need to be extradited?
This is too much to launder.
Well, then...
I don't want to be good.
I'm not sure how helpful that was.
I mean, all of our problems...
let's buy a bigger washing machine.
I am going to be great.
are because of those imperialist gringos!
And that's what they tried first.
A PAISA ROBIN HOOD
A drug dealer running
for president. It was crazy, right?
On paper, Pablo had
the most profitable taxi company ever.
No, stay there... stay there.
Well, not in Colombia.
Not in the mid-'80s.
As for the Ochoa brothers,
they went with a fancy PR firm
He only had three cars,
As far as Colombians go,
Pablo wasn't a drug dealer at all.
but he was pulling in
more than five million dollars a week.
and got ripped off because, well...
that's what PR agencies do.
He was a fucking winner.
And Gacha had the most successful
emerald mine of all time.
The living embodiment
of the Colombian dream.
"Better a grave in Colombia
The guy who'd buy houses for the poor
in exchange for nothing.
than a grave in the United States."
He would inject bad stones with oil
to make them shiny,
No, I've got it, Fabio, I've got it.
Let's see...
then have his friends in Miami
buy the emeralds with drug money
As far as Pablo could tell, the doors
to political success were there...
"Better a grave in Colombia
than a cell in the United States."
and give them as gifts
to hookers in town.
and all he had to do was to get to them.
- What do you think?
- I love it.
Everybody was happy.
Very good.
And in order to do that,
And for $50,000 more,
we'll make your logo.
But no matter what they did,
they couldn't hide all that money.
he asked Valeria Velez
to introduce him to Fernando Duque.
Done.
It just kept coming in.
By the way,
here's the logo $50,000 got you.
You're spending too much cash, Pablo.
Duque was a lawyer and a lobbyist
who represented the New Liberals,
In the upcoming presidential election,
extradition became the defining issue
You have Picassos, Dalís, farms,
a party who claimed
to represent the people.
amongst the candidates.
houses, apartments, boats, planes, cars...
Those the narcos could buy,
they bought.
The ones they could scare,
they scared.
I told you we have to fly low.
But Luis Carlos Galán was neither.
Pablo!
If you keep spending like that,
you're going to end up in Forbes Magazine.
I should've gotten into the taxi business.
And so, unable to buy him
and unable to scare him,
- Valeria, how are you doing?
- Well, thank you.
And if that happens,
the government is going to have our asses.
Mr. Duque.
Escobar tried out
that fancy new stationery,
Enough, Gustavo, enough.
It gives me great pleasure to invite you
to the Hacienda Nápoles.
and he wrote Galán a letter.
What do you want me to say?
- Nice to meet you.
- Please, come.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.MY-SUBS.com
Bury it.
After you, Valeria.
"And to conclude, I want
to express my most energetic protest
- How's that?
- Bury the cash.
And cut the bullshit.
Please.
over the improper interference
of North America
in a way that entails
the most flagrant violation
My fellow Americans...
Look, I am not a rich person.
I am a poor person with money.
Take Richard Nixon, for instance.
Go on, pussy.
of the sovereignty of our Motherland."
People forget,
but 47 million Americans voted for Nixon.
And that's what they did.
And for that reason,
I think that...
He's got some balls.
They buried it in fields...
Well, I think that
I understand the people
Escobar is shameless.
We thought he was one of the good guys.
The United States is inclined to support
your bid for the presidency, Mr. Galán.
And Nixon thought Chilean General Pinochet
was a good guy
they hid it in caletas,
hiding places in walls and ceilings.
to whom the New Liberalism
wants to give a voice.
The party clearly needs to hear
what you have to say, Mr. Escobar.
But even if we indict these narcos
in the United States,
because he hated the commies.
So we helped Pinochet seize power.
They even stuck a million dollars
in Pablo's mother's couch.
we still can't get them there
without Colombian approval.
There is a great deal of talk
about how you have made your money.
We're curious
as to your view on extradition.
I need guarantees
concerning the origins of your fortune.
Then Pinochet turned around
and killed thousands of people.
Hey, Mom.
My campaign manager,
Dr. Gaviria,
- I'm praying, Pablo.
- Just for a second.
doesn't want me
to stick my foot in my mouth.
And Valeria told you...
how much I am going to donate?
America wants Pablo Escobar
to prove they're winning a battle,
Maybe not such a good guy after all.
- No, no--
- Look, I am not a politician.
Sit.
I am not a successful lawyer like you.
I come from the street... brother.
when clearly,
they're losing a war.
I'll do what's best for Colombia.
I want to reassure you
that you will receive your piece.
But sometimes,
bad guys do good things.
It isn't very comfortable, Pablito.
If you speak in favor
of extradition, you will be their puppet,
- It's not about that--
- Assuming your piece is ten percent,
I'll buy you another sofa later.
and that will be your death sentence.
Nobody knows this, but back in '73,
Chile was on its way
Wouldn't it be better
if you put all this money in a bank, son?
your piece would be what?
$300,000 just for you.
I don't care about the Americans, but I am
still going to support extradition.
to being the world's biggest
cocaine processing and exporting center.
No.
All bankers are bandits.
Besides, if the gringos want to take away
all the goddamn killers of this country,
Really, honey?
Does that seem like a sufficient guarantee
for the Justice Minister or what?
then let them take them.
How many times do
I have to tell you not to waste the acid?
Since he couldn't get to Galán,
- Most definitely.
- All right, then.
Pablo reached out
to many of the country's judges.
They had deserts to hide the labs
and miles of unpatrolled coastline
Pablo called this accountant "Blackbeard,"
Let's go look at the hippos.
Come on.
He figured out that a sanctioned law
would do no harm
not because he looked like a pirate,
to ship the product north.
Blackie.
if no judge was willing to apply it.
To be productive,
you can't waste money! Come on!
but because his job was to map out
where the treasure was hidden.
Pablo?
"As you pass judgment
on one of our sons
You're surrounded!
But not even the pirate did the trick.
- And what about me?
- What about you?
- Hands up!
- Everybody on your knees!
and consider sending him
to his fate in the United States,
The problem was Colombia itself.
But Pinochet spoiled the party.
I don't get my piece?
know we, the Extraditables,
will pass judgment on you
What the fuck is going on here?
It was too small a country
for a fortune that big.
No, my queen.
The thing is that you...
On the ground!
It was inevitable... someone, somewhere
would try to snatch the narcos' treasure.
and bring a sentence far harsher."
He shut down 33 labs
and arrested 346 drug dealers.
you're in this for love, right?
The judges were so scared and intimidated
that special court procedures
had to be created.
Forbes Magazine says...
Look, Minister...
For the first time
in the history of Colombia,
And then, being Pinochet...
Escobar has founded schools, clinics.
that the narcos have more money
it was the good guys who
had to hide their faces behind the masks.
he had them all killed.
than the richest capitalist pig
in this country.
He has created sources of employment
throughout Medellín.
Defendants, please rise.
Attention!
The people love him,
and he loves the people.
Let me see?
Weapons ready!
And from a legal point of view,
his money is clean.
You've been tried and convicted
of cocaine trafficking.
Aim!
If we kidnap someone in their family,
what are they going to do?
And according to Forbes Magazine,
he's a drug trafficker.
You will immediately be turned over to the
DEA for extradition to the United States.
Ready ammunition!
Call the police?
Are you going to believe all of that
American imperialist propaganda?
Fire!
Commander.
It says here that Gacha, "The Mexican,"
is the ninth richest man in the world.
Take a look.
Despite his threats,
many brave men defied him.
I say we kidnap his son.
These are property holdings papers.
He's a psycho maniac, comrade.
And true to form,
when the pen failed...
They say when
a nuclear holocaust destroys the world,
Pablo was always ready with the sword.
Plus, he's bought off half the military.
Look.
only the cockroaches will survive.
He's the owner of hundreds of properties
in Colombia and also the United States.
Well, the Ochoa brothers
are number 14 on the list.
I guess they were right.
Their sister Marta
goes to the university.
In addition,
this man has no criminal record.
In light of this terrorism,
you'd think that everyone in Colombia
If there was,
there would be proof of his background.
The bullets missed Mateo Moreno,
aka Cockroach,
How about her?
would've made catching Escobar
the number one priority, right?
I like that more.
The Ochoas are soft.
Well, guess again.
and he was smart enough to play dead.
Communists. They're the real threat
to the security of this country.
How much is he paying you?
Wait a second.
All due respect, but Colombian cocaine has
killed more Americans than Soviet troops.
He wasn't killed on that day.
What about Pablo Escobar?
I am thinking about our party, Minister.
I know what you're thinking.
Escobar is prepared
to contribute millions of dollars.
We got FARC, we got M-19,
we got EPL, we got ELN,
Instead, he won the damn lottery.
No one's crazy enough
to kidnap drug dealers, right?
We already support Jairo Ortega
so that he can campaign in Antioquia.
all supported by the Soviets and Cubans.
But if you're thinking that, it's because
you're not familiar with M-19.
Sorry, Agent Peña, but our resources
gotta be directed at America's problems,
Cockroach had been
stealing from his bosses for months.
Let's let Escobar be his alternate.
M-19 was a communist guerrilla group
and you don't get to tell us
what those are.
Now he was left alone in the world
with the perfect product.
What do you prefer...
rumors and insinuations,
made up of college students
and intellectuals
Communists. Remember them?
A product whose offer
creates its own demand.
who read too much Karl Marx
for their own good.
or fewer representatives in Congress?
With Reagan in the White House,
it was hard to forget.
Start packing.
We have to leave the country.
And just like that...
an honest man blinked.
Their leader was
Ivan "the Terrible" Torres...
Fucking Pinochet
is killing the whole world.
In his words:
They are the focus of evil
in the modern world.
a history professor
who knew nothing about guerilla warfare,
You're not going back to that comuna!
- But you're not a communist.
- No, not a communist, something worse.
but understood the power of symbols.
What, you want me to stay
in this apartment for the next two years?
The Soviet evil empire
was Reagan's thing, always had been.
He broke into
the Quinta de Bolívar Museum
Oh, my God, you do.
A drug trafficker.
with his buddy Alejandro
and Alejandro's girlfriend, Elisa,
Honey, your cat was killed
as a warning to me.
In Hollywood, he named some actors
as communist sympathizers.
- A drug trafficker?
- Yes, a drug trafficker.
Our cat.
OK, our cat.
In Washington,
he created the Reagan Doctrine,
and stole a national treasure...
the sword of Simón Bolívar,
What if you went back to Miami just for
a little while until things quiet down?
which opposed Soviet-backed communists
all over the world.
Back then, we were just
finding out about the effects of cocaine
the mythic general who led Colombia
to independence from the Spanish empire.
- Oh, you're gonna make them quiet down?
- You're that good, huh?
Drug traffickers just didn't rate.
on the human brain.
I'll tell you what. I'll agree to go back
to Miami if you agree to go back, too.
You want to turn on the tap
of the richest country in the world,
We didn't know much, but we knew
it was some pretty powerful shit.
you'd better be chasing reds.
- You prepared to do that?
- I'm not giving in on this one!
Ambassador, if the CIA
and the Mil Group provide assets,
...this will give us better results, OK?
Cocaine hijacks
the pleasure centers in the brain.
the Colombians will get Escobar.
We're talking about a huge blow
to the cocaine trade
A rat will choose cocaine
over food and water.
- and saving thousands of lives...
- Ambassador.
It would choose cocaine over sleep,
over sex... over life itself.
The CIA agrees with Mil Group.
Pablo Escobar is no longer a congressman.
These jokers even left a note:
OK. I'll be waiting to take you home.
I already stick out like a sore thumb.
The human brain
isn't quite the same as a rodent's...
"Bolívar, your sword
returns to the battlefield."
The bodyguards
are only gonna draw more attention.
He's just a wanted Colombian
drug trafficker, and as such,
Just humor me.
he is not a direct threat to our country's
strategic interests in South America.
unless we're talking about cocaine.
It was a stroke of genius...
a marketing stunt way ahead of its time.
I can't do my job
if I'm worried about your safety.
And it made them famous overnight.
Mm...
The CIA would prefer not to get involved
in local police problems.
Cockroach knew
he had the perfect product.
And I guess it went to their heads.
Let the Colombians get him.
Hey, mind parking
down the street a little?
He just needed to smuggle it
to the right markets.
What about Pablo Escobar?
He's the richest of them all.
I'll scream if I need you.
Noonan really thinks
allocating $100,000
Gracias.
- will be enough to go after Escobar.
- Yeah, it's a fucking joke.
Escobar gives money to the poor.
And the best smugglers in the world
were in Colombia.
You're right.
Escobar is a man of the people.
That's about what he spends on shoes,
isn't it?
WELCOME TO COLOMBIA
The CNP has zero chance
of capturing him with that bullshit.
He's all right with me.
OK, then.
- Buenos días, Father.
- Connie.
So what do we do now?
Like Goldilocks,
he had three options.
Let's do the Ochoas.
What, are you surprised to see me?
We've had American volunteers.
They come and go.
Use what little we got
to try to even the odds.
And pay attention, because all three
are important to this story.
Well, this one will keep coming.
It's true,
the hundred grand wasn't that much.
But delivered into the right hands,
it could make a difference.
The Ochoa brothers:
Jorge, that's Fabio on the horse.
Surprised to see Elisa,
a communist M-19 guerrilla,
There were a lot of good cops in Colombia,
honorable men.
A typical Colombian smuggling family.
working in the comuna?
That's because you don't know
the liberation church in Colombia.
But the head of counternarcotics,
General Jaramillo, wasn't one of 'em.
- They were smart and rich...
- Salud!
And the priest... innocent, right?
...but Cockroach felt the high life
had made 'em too soft.
Wrong.
He's more of a commie than she is.
And as such,
he was exactly what we needed.
Another possible partner
was José Rodríguez Gacha,
Who is the gringa?
Thank you for seeing me, General.
March 13th, 1981,
the day they kidnapped Marta Ochoa,
A child of God, just like you.
You're welcome.
nicknamed "The Mexican,"
for his love of tequila and sombreros.
Hm. Got it.
Listen, I have General Gomez
assigned to the operation against Pablo.
He dominated the emerald smuggling routes.
was also the day the Lion
completed 100 trips to Miami.
With all due respect, General Jaramillo...
I propose Horacio Carrillo.
Let's see, you are here for a cat?
But Carrillo only acts on his own orders.
He doesn't follow anyone.
Hola.
This isn't just any cat.
This is a gringo cat of the DEA.
Well, I don't want him to follow.
Emeralds are a pretty rough trade,
even by Colombian standards.
Good afternoon.
- What's he saying?
- I'm telling him about the cat.
I want him to lead.
If you make it to the top...
- Mr. and Mrs. Murphy.
- Sí.
And what you want
is for me to find a cat killer.
it means you've killed your enemies.
Does the cat have any papers?
It was the narcos, Suárez.
We don't take this shit lightly.
Go ahead.
- Sí.
- Please.
Hey, partner. What are you doing here?
Yes, General.
And sometimes, your partners.
Your friend is a little crazy.
As you wish.
Thank you.
No hablo español.
I don't know what you're saying.
Understood.
I don't speak English.
Cockroach worried that the emerald trade
had made Gacha too hard.
Mm.
Get me some information, Suárez.
What happened, honey?
Things with work.
Look, I don't have enough people
When will Horacio arrive
to have dinner with us?
So he zeroed in on his third option:
a man Cockroach knew would be just right.
Excuse me a second, please.
to go through hundreds of hours of chatter
over a fucking cat.
I'm making the chicken he likes,
but he's out with the girlfriend.
If this was information about the narcos,
yes, my people are interested.
But they won't give a fuck about the cat.
Tell me what's wrong.
Yeah, you guessed it: Pablo Escobar.
- What is he saying?
- They don't like cats in this country.
They want me to catch Pablo Escobar.
Sir, this couple has no sanitary B-47 form
Tell me about it.
The man who would
change my life forever.
But if you want
to put all my people to work
and no I-435
identifying papers, either.
to find out who killed the fucking cat,
that is going to cost you more.
The Ochoas aren't happy at all.
Pablo was making a killing
in the smuggling business.
Well, I guess he's talking about Puff.
Yes, sir.
They brought an American cat with them.
They're saying that since
you've become a wanted man,
Cigarettes, alcohol, marijuana,
you name it.
bribing the police
has gotten very costly.
Sure, but without the I-435, I can't
officially state that it is indeed a cat.
They broke into the house to kill his cat.
At the time,
Pablo owned half the police in Medellín.
They want to renegotiate
the price of our routes.
I think they made him
when he arrived at the airport in Bogotá.
Hm.
But DAS was Colombia's version of the FBI.
Find out.
When it came to me killing
to get their sister back, well, then...
I also can't guarantee
that it's American.
They didn't play by the same rules.
- Is that a D-103?
- Yup.
I didn't hear them complaining, did I?
Let me get this straight.
Gotta pay this cop off for information,
Yeah. The problem is that
it is one thing to kill communists
Good day.
Sir, I'm not trying
to make your life more difficult.
- and another to kill politicians.
- So what now?
- then you gotta get a receipt?
- I gotta get reimbursed.
Pablo Escobar?
Where's Felipo?
What I would do is increase
the payments to the police, you know?
Felipo's been arrested.
OK, sir.
This gentleman is an employee
of the American Embassy in our country,
Bullshit. Felipo works for me.
And most of all, to the top brass.
He used to work for you. Now he's going
to jail. What do you think about that?
My boss is not having a good day.
and he assures me that you gave out his
personal information to certain criminals.
We're already giving too much money
to those bastards.
- Do you know who you're talking to?
- Shut the fuck up.
I think his wife left him.
Mm.
- I wasn't talking to you.
- Relax, Gustavo, please.
That's not true.
Oh, shit. What's that?
Is it snowing or what?
Show some respect.
Yeah, well, he's a little bit cranky,
so... how important is this cat to you?
These guys killed his cat.
Egrets from the Himalayas.
Now what's the problem,
Mr. Jose Luis?
Maybe you don't know this,
but the mistreatment of animals
Excuse me?
It took two years
to train them to stay there.
OK.
is a federal crime.
How do you know my name?
Come with me, please.
Is this funny to you?
They cost me a million dollars.
You're Colonel Jose Luis Herrera.
They can bring formal charges against you,
and you could lose your job.
And that's Nacho Ibarra.
Do you not need your job, Santiago?
Bastards.
There's Garcia, Lopez...
Yes, I need it.
Stay in the fucking tree!
- Is that Pinilla?
- Yes, Pinilla.
- That's Pinilla.
- Yeah.
Pinilla...
and with Phillipe is Esparanza.
I don't give a rat's ass.
Open the fucking trucks.
So... wait here, please.
Mr. Murphy,
do you recognize these men?
I don't have all day.
And my boss will ask you
for this paper later.
Seems like you lost that dough,
eh, cousin?
Yeah, you guys
stalled me at the airport
How long is it gonna be?
so you could take my passport
and copy and scan it, didn't you?
That's your problem, Pablo.
Open it.
I don't know.
- What?
- May I?
You think that everything
can be controlled,
but it turns out that nature
cannot be controlled.
Pablo! Pablo!
You both are being accused
of conspiring against a federal agent
OK, OK, OK, Gustavo... OK.
While I was trying to get into Bogotá,
of the United States.
Pablo was trying to get into politics.
Tell me something, Mr. Escobar.
The cat is under the jurisdiction
of the American government.
When he said he was going
to be president of Colombia, he meant it.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Your English is really good.
You don't even bother
to hide your contraband.
- Hello, Pablo.
- Hello, Valeria.
And to kill it is the same
as to kill a police dog.
Thank you. I took a course
at the University of Antioquia.
Because I pay for the privilege, Colonel.
- This is my wife, Tata.
- Hello.
How long you been at the comuna?
Oh, yeah? You don't say.
This is absurd.
Just a few weeks.
Where are your import papers?
Don't worry.
Everything will be perfect.
Look, I'm a Colombian citizen,
and I know exactly my--
Is your husband
gonna help us here, too?
You need papers for these TV sets.
I'm just not used
to these type of things.
I saw him when he dropped you off.
What does he do?
Take them.
Just be yourself.
You will not disrespect them!
Oh, he's, uh... head of janitorial
services at the US Embassy.
Sorry, Mr. Escobar. We're not
Medellín police making a shit salary.
Ma'am, it would be best
if you weren't here.
Is that clear?
If I open my mouth, they kill me...
and they kill my wife.
Look, Tata,
there are a lot of people here.
- Look, brother, it's not for you.
- Then who?
It's for Carlitos.
It might not be good for the baby.
He's having problems with his wife.
Your son.
Go to the house.
Shut up!
- I fucked up.
- How?
Carrillo got the job
just like you wanted.
Wouldn't he like a TV in his room?
- Imbecile.
- OK, gentlemen.
No, Jaramillo's sending a message.
This is quite simple.
Hey, Pinilla!
I can get the phone number of the person
to whom you sent those documents,
He's telling me I got his price wrong.
He's setting Carrillo up for failure,
and when he does fail,
Your daughter just
got her driver's license, right?
he'll fire him for incompetence,
and me and you,
we lose the only cop we can trust.
I've got some car stereo systems in there
that are really cool. Real nice.
Where is this guy?
We've been waiting for hours now.
and I can tell him that you accused him
of being the cat killer.
Maybe he's at "terapia de pareja."
How does that sound?
- Hey!
- Sorry I'm late, honey.
- Mm...
That friend of yours, Lopez...
he's got a wife that's really beautiful.
What's that?
Couples counseling.
Javier, this is my friend, Elisa.
- Right? She's a fox.
- Yeah.
Right.
I sent a copy of that passport...
- Javier works with Steve.
- Nice to meet you.
What're you doing?
Nice to meet you.
Your wife is gorgeous, brother.
Oh, I'm practicing my Spanish.
to a man they call...
Are you another... janitor at the embassy,
like Steve?
What's she doing with a guy like you?
Welcome to Nuevos Tiempos.
I'm Valeria Velez and I'm here with the
man known as "the Robin Hood of the poor"
"Poison."
No, actually, I'm CIA.
But that's classified,
so don't tell anybody.
for his generosity
with the poor of Medellín.
OK, Poison.
You're going to take this money
to Fernando Duque in Bogotá.
I'm here to hunt communists
and prevent a Marxist invasion from Cuba.
I think she deserves some jewelry, no?
Yeah, you heard that right.
She just compared Pablo Escobar
to fucking Robin Hood.
And this is the address.
- The janitor thing, what, that was you?
- Mm.
Why don't I have my boys
drop off a few gifts?
And in a way, she was right.
If they stop you on the road,
just salute the official,
No, it's just a cover.
give them a little bribe
and continue forward.
- Thank you for being so honest.
- Mm-hm.
When you've run out of ways
to hide your money,
that's when you give it to the poor.
No violence.
Just so you know,
I'm a communist guerrillera.
Colonel, how is your mom doing?
But I don't want to get ahead of myself.
And you call me every two hours.
- Of course, boss. Whatever you say.
- OK, then. No showing off.
- She just got out of the hospital, right?
- Yes, she's feeling better.
Tell us about your program,
"Medellín Without Slums," Mr. Escobar.
Perfect.
No showing off!
If we had known at the time
she was telling the truth...
- Good. That makes us happy, right?
- Yes.
I was born in Rionegro,
not too far from here.
- Nice and simple. Go unnoticed.
- Got it.
we probably wouldn't have cared.
Gentlemen...
And I asked myself how a government
that exists for the people
What the fuck are you doing?
We cared about Pablo Escobar.
I'm going to tell you who I am.
And catching him...
wasn't gonna be easy.
can be so out of touch
with what they need.
He had better resources
and better information.
I am Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria.
Getting ready, right?
Hospitals, social and athletic programs,
You are meeting up with politicians,
not with gangsters.
And at the time,
he owned over 800 homes and fincas,
My eyes are everywhere.
plus the construction
of 400 houses in this community.
surrounded by dozens of sicarios
willing to die for him.
That means you guys
can't move a finger in all of Antioquia
I hear you told your mother that one day
you would be president of Colombia.
Aren't they the same thing, boss?
And cops...
he owned a lot of them, too.
without me knowing about it.
Politicians scare easily.
Do you understand? Not a finger.
Do you have any political aspirations,
Mr. Escobar?
But not all of them.
None at all.
My business takes up most of my time.
You're fine with just a pistol.
Jaramillo's intel says Pablo's gonna be
at his finca called El Bizcocho tomorrow.
Go to it, then.
Go to it, dumbass.
One day, I'm going to be
President of the Republic of Colombia.
I will tell you one thing, Valeria.
The only way to surprise him
is an aerial assault.
According to CNP wiretaps,
the sicario "Poison"
For decades, our country has been led by
Lopez and other families that are wealthy
Jaramillo didn't give us a helicopter.
was recorded saying
he was driving to Bogotá this afternoon.
So look, I make deals for a living.
Then we need to figure out
where he's hiding today.
For what purpose,
we don't know.
But if we don't respond
to the obvious threat to Agent Murphy,
Now, you can stay calm
and accept my deal...
who made their fortune
off exploiting the poor.
They don't know what
common people dream of, but I do...
we're sending the wrong message.
Trapped a little bird.
or accept the consequences.
Police have the information,
then they should make the arrest.
And I'm gonna make sure that he sings.
Connie, you know who that is?
No. No, if we leave it to them,
someone will sell us out.
Jesus.
Bet he could get our cat
into the country.
The narcos have informants
in their department.
Silver...
What Peña's driving at is that
Major Carrillo should man a roadblock.
I can't believe it.
or lead.
- We can trust Carrillo.
- I don't have authority
Just remember that you wanted all in.
They don't even know
he's a fucking drug dealer.
- over the Colombian police.
- All due respect, Ambassador,
You decide.
- Thank you very much.
- Pablo! Pablo! Pablo!
Hand me that coffee.
but you know where we are.
With enough money,
you can get anything done.
- Let 'em go. Let 'em go.
- All right, then.
At the time,
Pablo was just a blip on my radar.
Excuse me for saying so...
but this isn't much of a roadblock, is it?
I didn't know
I was about to be a blip on his.
Well, if the roadblock is too obvious,
Pablo can be tipped off
by a cop or by a passerby, who knows.
He already gave up
the name of three fincas,
but Pablo's not gonna be at any of them.
Can anybody in this country
keep a secret?
Well, we've been waiting
for hours. Thanks for coming out.
But you do know
where he is hiding, don't you?
Uh, my wife's a little exhausted,
so here is the cat's vaccination--
I've got a spotter set up
about four kilometers away.
He's gonna let us know
when Poison passes.
Your passport.
You're gonna question them, right?
Because we need to--
Poison's killed three of my men already.
I'm sorry?
If I catch him alive,
you guys can question him here.
Your passport, please.
Then you guys gotta go.
Gracias.
Hey, hey, hey, hold on, 65?
Sixty-five.
Look, little brother,
Hey, brother, that's a lot.
I know it scares the shit out of you
that Pablo will kill you.
You sure?
I counted every single son of a bitch.
What do you do at
the United States Embassy, Mr. Murphy?
All right!
But I will also kill you.
Yo, Pablo!
Sure, but are you counting
what happened last night?
And very slowly.
I am in, uh,
janitorial services.
Pablo is going to kill me more slowly.
- This is Pablo.
- Hello.
Of course,
that was number 65.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mateo Moreno.
Janitorial services.
Don't bullshit.
I was the one who shot that faggot.
Well, then, you should pray we find him,
and quickly.
No, no, no.
"Cockroach" to my friends.
Another one.
- Bullshit.
- Bullshit...
All right,
yesterday we were talking,
Your embassy must be very clean.
and I think this business
can make us a lot of money.
if I was the one
who killed that little man.
Oh, yeah.
You bet your ass it is.
You only shot him
once he was already on the ground, dead.
We knew that Escobar would
get a heads-up the second we moved out,
Explain.
I shot him first.
but there was a small part of me
that thought, in his arrogance,
Well... I get the paste in Peru.
Your cat's cleared.
I will handle
the chemical part of production,
he would stand and fight.
and all the other details
in producing this exquisite white powder.
Enjoy Colombia.
Or maybe we just wanted
to send him a message.
Come in.
What I need from you
is to help me get it into Colombia.
Boss!
Did you give information about Poison
to the DEA?
Poison...
Now tell him how much it costs.
So?
Boss!
And just like that, the narcos
had me on file the very first day.
I'm still listening
to their phone conversations,
They were headed for El Bizcocho,
but they got off the main highway.
In Chile, this little thing
costs ten bucks a gram.
and it's not a shipment of drugs.
They're carrying
three million dollars to Bogotá,
- They're already on their way here.
- How far are they?
- They sell it by grams?
- Yes, it's very good. Look...
and if two guys from the DEA
stop that car,
Two hours, boss.
Round up the guys,
and tell them to get ready.
You do a little bit, and in 20 minutes,
you want to do some more.
Pablo is going to hang you by the balls.
- We're leaving.
- All right.
Also...
- You don't have 65, Poi.
- Yes, I do.
it's a digestive aid.
It makes you want to take a shit.
We have to go.
It's very clean, this stuff.
Want some?
Eh!
Go where?
The police are coming.
What are you doing, Gonorrhea?!
- But Pablo, I've been cooking for hours.
- I'm sorry, my love,
If this is really that good
and we can make some money,
As for Valeria Velez,
- but we need to leave now.
- What about our things? Our clothes?
we can find room on our trucks.
the journalist who first
interviewed Pablo... watch out.
Look, 65, man!
We can sell it in Bogotá, Barranquilla,
Cali, Cartagena...
We'll buy new ones later,
won't we?
We're going to be rich.
She was as dangerous as M-19.
Now we're going
to have to wash the car, man!
- What did you say your name was?
- Cockroach.
Son of a bitch.
I'm sorry.
Yes?
Do you hear me complaining?
Well look, Cuca...
Hi, Pablo.
I have good news for you.
you don't have any vision,
my friend.
I'm going to help you
avoid an enormous loss.
As long as you're with us, Pablo,
I'm prepared to do whatever it takes.
And how much is it going to cost me?
If it costs ten dollars a gram here...
Ten percent... $300,000.
Does your wife do it standing up?
imagine how much
it will sell for in Miami.
Aah!
Don't ever disrespect Tata.
- How did you find out?
- One of your men.
I love that song.
That Poison... he talks too much.
- Bring all of the boxes here.
- Yes, sir.
Rodrigo! One more.
Do you hear me?
You should take his phone away.
- Cangrejo!
- Yes?
Go to Pablo's room
and see if anything is in there.
Five percent.
I'm sorry, Pablo...
I'm sorry.
- Efrain!
- Yeah?
The two blue notebooks
are the only ones I'm taking.
Forgive me.
Suspicious vehicle approaching.
OK. We have visual
confirmation. Four kilometers away.
Search the whole house to make sure
that not a single loose document remains.
Yes, sir!
It won't happen again.
I promise.
Back then, Miami was a paradise.
- Hello?
- Poison?
You bring your fucking mouth
back here immediately!
I signed up for the sand,
surf and women.
How can I apologize? Huh?
- Yes. I'm sorry, boss.
- Now!
In '79, the bad guys I was chasing
wore flip-flops.
What's wrong, Gustavo?
The son of a bitch policeman
tapped my phone!
DEA! Stop!
I was a young DEA agent,
partnered with my buddy, Kevin Brady.
- These fags.
- You have a very big mouth, Poison.
You fucked us, Pablo.
Not only you and me.
Pablo is really pissed off.
Kevin was a little slow afoot.
Shut that mug,
or you will never reach 66, you hear?
You fucked the whole family.
Why you running, huh?
Want to put it in my ass? Hm?
But of course, since you needed
to present yourself to Congress...
What you got?
What is this? Huh?
What is that?
That right there...
that's a goddamn promotion.
You gotta give it to her.
since you want to be president
of this motherfucking country,
Let's go celebrate.
She saw Pablo coming a mile away.
OK!
the rest of us get screwed,
isn't that right?
- Whoo!
- Look at that.
And she got herself in just the
right place to take full advantage of him.
Go! Go! Go!
I'm calling this off. Nobody's coming.
But what the fuck...
How you like me now?
Not unlike my partner Javier Peña,
How much money you owe me?
who figured the best way
to get inside narco information
- What the fuck has happened here?
- Maybe Poison spotted the spotter.
a man only dies once, right?
What happened to the money
you owed me last week?
was to hang out
with the same women they did.
That's right, that's right.
Either that or Suárez sold you out.
Yeah, if he did,
he must've had a better offer,
Come here.
All right.
All right, who do we pick?
and it wasn't a fucking cat.
How 'bout her?
No, no, no,
we gotta fuck with him.
- Yeah, let's mess with his head.
- Um...
He has been called the "Paisa Robin Hood,"
My brother.
Oh, right there.
See her? At the bar?
but he is much more than that.
I'm going to let you sit
next to the pilot. Come on, come on.
- Which one?
- Blue top, blond hair. That's his type.
He is a man to whom the people
mean a great deal. All of us.
- Oh! Strike!
- She's hot.
There we go.
To avoid suspicion
and questioning about his fortune,
- All right.
- Whoo!
Murph! Sparrow, three o'clock.
Pablo ran as an alternate
for Jairo Ortega,
Hey, while you were walking back,
she was checking your ass out.
a former congressman from Antioquia.
Oh, she was checking out your ass.
Get the fuck outta here.
Come on.
It was the first time an alternate was
more important than the main candidate.
Listen, she eye-fucked you
the entire time you were bowling.
I like to think
that as Pablo looked down
We get better every time we practice.
on Hacienda Nápoles for the last time,
She was. She was eye-fucking you.
The entire time.
You're amazing, Javier.
he got our message...
and I hope it really pissed him off.
I'm serious, I'm serious. Look at her.
Well...
I am tired... of the
people with power running this country.
You may have 800 houses, my friend,
but none of them is home.
- Uh-huh. That's his type.
- Talking about the blond one?
No, the other one.
Of course the blond one.
don't go overboard.
We will keep you on the run
for the rest of your life,
She's the hottest one there.
She's your type.
This is a fight between the people
with power and poor people, weak people.
You dicking me around?
or until we catch you...
or kill you.
From now on,
nowhere is safe.
It's the truth.
And this fight must begin here!
Fuck it, I'm going in.
- Go get her.
- Mm!
What can you offer me to drink?
- Yup.
- Hey, while you're up there,
Whiskey or tap water.
get us another pitcher, will ya?
To have power does not mean
that one can abuse the poor.
- Pace yourself.
- Look at him. Look at his swagger.
Water.
If I am elected...
if my friend, Jairo, is elected...
those who have never had a voice
will have a voice.
What you're missing
in this apartment is a woman.
The only people to detain
were the maids and the gardeners
How you doing?
while we searched the finca
from top to bottom.
Busy.
It's fine the way it is.
Those who are hungry will have food.
I just said, "Look, if you don't
wanna be there, you don't have to be.
Well, I wasn't offering.
The dirt-poor cops
were astounded by the luxury.
Those who want to learn will have schools.
No one's forcing you to do anything."
So, I don't know...
Hey, if you're risking your life
for $22 a week... you'd pig out, too.
And those who have dreams
will see that there are no limits
to what you can achieve.
Yeah, those bastards got me.
There's an old saying in law enforcement:
Here.
In me, you have a friend
But I couldn't let it end like that.
"The bad guys
need to get lucky every time.
Excuse me.
See those guys over there?
whom you have always had,
The good guys
just need to get lucky once."
If you were a client,
you would have paid me already.
the friend of today, the friend
of yesterday and the friend of tomorrow.
Uh, they're fucking with me.
And in the ashes of Pablo's hasty exit,
I got very lucky.
Telling me you were checking out my ass,
and who checks out a cop's ass, right?
You're a cop?
- And you wouldn't know my real name.
- Don't take it the wrong way.
The address I found led us to a
nondescript building in downtown Medellín.
Not a cop, actually. I'm DEA.
It's cash from Uncle Sam
for the information you never gave me.
Thank you very much.
Drug Enforcement?
- Pablo! Pablo! Pablo!
- Thank you very much.
We raided it,
and guess who we found?
So you're the one
making pot more expensive.
Come on, why don't you do me a favor?
Blackbeard.
Take it.
Pablo's number one accountant
and keeper of all secrets.
I wanna show these guys up.
Why don't you, uh...
give me your phone number?
And my visa?
My friend, Jairo Ortega!
In custody,
he would describe a cocaine empire
How about a fake number?
Give me something I can use
and we'll talk about it.
that was bringing in $60 million a day.
That'll work.
Hey, buddy, you got a pen?
Pablo was bigger than General Motors.
Pablo! Pablo! Pablo!
The mountain of evidence filled
an entire room in the Palace of Justice,
What are you doing this weekend?
- I'm going to Medellín.
- Work or play?
Thank you very much.
home of Colombia's supreme court,
the only place
thought safe enough to store it.
I have to take care of my child.
I can pay, too.
We had enough evidence
to put him away for 100 lifetimes.
- You were marvelous, my love.
- You sure?
- I'm sorry for the trouble.
- Sure.
- Yes.
- Very good, Pablo.
Fuck.
Have a good night.
Those guys are richer
than Uncle Sam, Javi.
There are a few things we can improve,
but we'll work on them.
Fuck.
OK, whatever you say.
- What's up?
- Jaramillo's running the show.
Aah...
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much, Valeria.
Come here.
He's pissed we only gave him 100 grand.
Shot down!
Congratulations, ma'am.
He's not letting us
make any copies of anything.
- Where's the pitcher at?
- The pitcher? Oh, I...
- What?
- Give me a kiss.
Excuse me.
Javi, there's some good stuff in here,
stuff we can use.
I didn't make it back
with the pitcher.
Give me a kiss.
None of it can leave the room.
I just came up with this and
I couldn't read it. What does that say?
The narcos have been
paying some guy named Ellis McPickle
- Read it and weep!
- Aw... Gimme that.
- to run coke all over the place.
- Ellis McPickle?
How much did that cost you?
I'm assuming that it's an alias.
- That's your handwriting.
- It's not my handwriting!
To vote for Jairo Ortega
is to vote for the one and only Pablo!
I guess I'll have to find another girl.
Good luck with that.
We're all going to Medellín.
Take 'em.
I figured, what the hell.
Some of us are even going by plane.
Tata, what's wrong?
- What?
- Just stuff 'em down your pants.
Worst that could happen,
I'd wake up some grandmother in Boca.
What are you talking about?
Helena?
Do you want to catch Pablo
or not?
Helena.
Why does that woman need to know
everything about each step you take?
What are you talking about?
Hello?
Whose party is it?
- Valeria Velez.
- My love...
- Why me?
- Because they'll suspect me.
So it wasn't a fake.
- They won't suspect you.
- What if they search me?
I thought you might figure it out.
Tata, she's a newspaper woman,
a reporter who follows the news.
They're not gonna
search a white boy, OK?
After all, you're DEA.
- You're a guest in their country.
- Guests don't steal.
And just like that... she had me.
Oh, God! What was that?
And right now, I'm the news.
Just do it.
That was like a .38.
Sometimes you gotta do bad things
to catch bad people.
- About four blocks away.
- Oh...
When you win, don't disrespect me
anymore with that bitch.
The minute Pablo laid his eyes
on the paste-processing labs in Peru,
- And sometimes, bad people...
- Señor.
Come here.
Come here, come here, come here.
...help you do good things.
cocaine had him.
Slowly... come on.
These are
from the narcos' account in Miami.
Come on.
A cashier's check
payable to "Ellis McPickle."
It's been a while.
These are my friends,
Pablo and Gustavo.
You are going to be the First Lady
of this country one of these days.
Yes.
Would you like a little coffee?
Welcome to Bogotá.
I've heard that name mentioned
in some of the narco wiretap transcripts.
Yeah, a coffee?
Therefore, you are going
to have to learn to deal with the press.
Yes, a coffee.
- How about you, Pablo?
- No.
Should we do it under the bed?
Obviously, it's an alias.
You sure?
That woman is not on your level, Pablo.
No Colombian would go by the name
"Ellis McPickle."
My factory is small,
but highly productive.
She degrades you.
Please, don't worry about Valeria.
Because he's not Colombian.
Look. For crushing the leaves, I like to
use children because of their tiny feet.
He's an American pilot who transports
tons of cocaine for the cartel.
Pablo!
Little magic leaves.
- A gringo?
- Mm-hm.
The kerosene
separates the drug from the leaf.
A car, please!
- What's his name?
- We don't know.
Over here, the sulfuric acid
distills and distills it.
A car to the hospital, now!
But we do know that Gustavo
frequently mentions "McPickle."
Then you cut it,
and mix it with gasoline.
Just one thing...
Who told you about this?
Suarez, do you ever worry
what will happen to you
if Pablo finds out
that you work for both sides?
Then, basically, you pull the merchandise
out of the liquid.
You know what, Pablo?
Mother Teresa of Calcutta.
To me, it looks like
you are handling things very badly.
- I'm on your side.
- Yeah?
Let it dry, dry, dry.
You use ammonia to get the paste.
Then prove it.
What else can you tell me about McPickle?
And here it is.
It's pasty... but pure.
You need to start thinking more
about your family... and about business.
We have his photograph
in some of our files.
Here is the prize.
Pablo says they're
not going to pay a dime for Marta Ochoa.
Thing is,
you can't be a politician.
It's like the kitchen in your house.
Says who?
But maybe you should check with the CIA.
He started his career with them.
Like baking a cake.
Gustavo, too.
- And Jorge?
- No. Jorge doesn't agree.
You can't go strutting around
giving things to people
Only a much better cake
than you've ever had.
simply so they will love you.
- Then what?
- They're all going to a meeting.
Wha... What the fuck is this?
We... are bandits.
This is me giving you homework.
Look, an old press, an antique.
At Las Margaritas.
Former CIA pilot
flying coke for the narcos.
- Everyone?
- Yeah, they'll all be there.
And I need you to find out who it is.
First off, I don't fucking work for you,
Murphy, you hear me?
Now we put it in the oven.
If you run for Congress, find someone else
to manage the laboratories.
- So don't come in here thinking that...
- Is that Barry Seal?
Here's one.
The other will follow.
Señor Escobar?
All natural, organic and healthy.
Very good.
First day at the American Embassy.
Come meet your daughter.
What's he up to these days?
Well...
- I met my partner...
- Javier?
Barry Seal.
- we'll take a kilo.
- A whole kilo. Perfect.
...who introduced me to the DEA.
Murphy, this is Weaver and Wisnicki.
- No.
- You said a kilo.
These guys are R.I.P.
"Retired in Place."
God has blessed us with a girl, Pablo.
Barry Seal, a good ol'
Southern boy who loved college football,
We'll take five.
- Eat me, Peña.
- Paid vacation's over, fellas.
How do we get five across the border?
Murphy and I are going to Medellín.
mind-altering chemicals,
and pussy...
We'll telex the T-3 reports.
They go straight to Washington.
How beautiful.
which made him perfect CIA material.
That's Gustavo's department.
We are going to Medellín?
But his expensive lifestyle
also made him perfect narco material.
Shh.
- Then the Mil Group.
- Jarheads... this is Murphy.
Shh.
Finding Barry was easy.
This one has got a good engine.
Murphy, this is Mil Group.
We just had to stake out
his favorite whorehouse.
I was taking a look at it,
and the best place to hide the merchandise
They advise Colombian military
on communist threats in the countryside.
would be under the rear wheel well.
Hey, those are classified.
It just so happened
to be Peña's favorite, too.
It's 22 and one half horsepower.
- Now they're declassified.
- That's the ambassador's call.
A friend of mine told me about this place.
I've never been here before.
Is this easy to take off?
Don't worry about that shit.
I'll stick five kilos in there easy.
No problem.
No, I'm serious.
All right, all right.
I'll take three cars, please.
Look.
- Sure, when do you need them?
- Now, brother.
And the last stop...
the ambassador's office.
Oh, my God.
That's Freckles. I know her.
Until next time.
All right, we'll take the cars
and head back to the lab.
Why do you need this intel?
There's an unusual number of prostitutes
headed to Medellín this weekend.
Why the fuck
are we going back to the lab?
Pablo is out of control.
- Goddamn, is that Barry?
- Or should we say McPickle?
Because there are four wheel wells per car
and that's 20 kilos.
Every high-end girl in Bogotá.
First class airfare,
five-star hotels.
Mother Mary, man.
What do you want us to do?
Come on, we got you a ride
waiting over here.
The narcos are having a meeting
and then a party.
For three cars, that's 60 kilos.
What does the M-19
have to do with this?
You can't give Pablo Escobar a spanking
as though he were some spoiled brat.
Hi, Vanessa.
So if it's nine dollars
profit per gram, what?
Somebody kidnapped Marta Ochoa.
Intel suggests it was M-19.
It's fun to say, though,
ain't it? "McPickle"?
$9,000 per kilo.
I need access to the M-19 files
to confirm.
Oh, no?
$9,000 times 60...
The profit is $540,000.
And why not?
Careful with the threat
you cannot execute.
That's it!
If I find out one single dollar
of American taxpayer money
Have a seat, Barry.
- Do you know how to drive, Cockroach?
- Yeah.
went to any of those hookers,
it'll be your ass.
OK, Pablo and I drive fast.
That's half a million dollars... per trip,
OK, thank you.
One last thing, Ambassador.
You know what he's doing, right?
You seem awful relaxed for someone
who's facing life in the clink.
Yes, Agent Peña?
According to Colombian law,
a congressman has total immunity.
using the same smuggling routes
he always used.
I'm filing a visa request
for my informant. I need your signature.
Well, you guys ain't got shit.
You're bothering me.
Do you think he's protecting himself
while we remain in the drift?
We got records from Escobar listing
shipments from Medellín to Louisiana
Easiest money he ever made.
She sure likes you.
Is your informant really a prostitute?
I do. He thinks he's that fucking
"Paisa Robin Hood."
- to the tune of 500 tons?
- Yeah.
Everybody works for somebody.
So what do we do?
Yeah? Well, let's see
if that holds up in court, huh?
Back in Medellín,
Pablo didn't waste any time.
Well... we fulfill our duties,
stuffing the ballot box,
The funny thing is you can't make
a direct flight from Medellín to Louisiana
He bought a house
in his old neighborhood
and opened his first lab to turn
Peruvian paste... into cocaine powder.
and later we let Pablo receive
the applause, and take the risk.
without making a refueling stop.
The very next day,
I was flying with Peña to Medellín,
Yeah, according to the records,
you made stops in Cuba and Nicaragua.
How are you feeling, Gustavo?
Pablo's home turf.
We continue with our business...
in the shadows, like always.
The manifests don't lie.
All this smells like shit to me.
An ex-CIA man making stops in communist
countries with or without cocaine,
What an ignorant bastard.
It's like French cheese.
Carlos, what are the guys saying?
that would be considered treason
by the US Justice Department, wouldn't it?
The stinkier, the better.
First stop: Carlos Holguín School,
Colonel Carrillo's base of operations.
I imagine that they're worried, right?
Well, damn...
you guys are good.
All right.
They are not politically conscious,
brother.
What about all these lights?
Communist sympathizer.
We're gonna wrap you up
in a big, red bow
Is that to tip off the cops,
or what?
and drop you right off
at Reagan's doorstep.
Just worry about transporting the stuff
and selling it.
How can you expect them
to understand your objectives?
Using Cuba and Nicaragua
as refueling stops for coke shipments,
that's treason and trafficking.
I'm the artist here, clear?
- Good day, Major.
- Good day.
What's that,
two life sentences for the price of one?
You do understand me, brother.
Clear.
Your intel was good. The traquetos
are gathering at Las Margaritas.
- Right?
- Yeah. Mm-mm.
That's right.
It was a mom-and-pop operation,
so small they called it The Kitchen.
Imagine... a state governed by us.
I want you
to meet our new DEA, Steve Murphy.
Well... see,
I figured this day might come.
But make no mistake,
it would change Medellín forever.
Fresh meat.
Immunity for everyone, brother.
We, Carlos, belong to the people.
Why don't you uncuff me, boys.
I got something to show you.
You know the thing
that has me worried, Pablo?
Then we went straight to a fancy
hotel where the narcos were about to meet.
I need you to use your influence with the
others to convince them that I am right.
Yeah? What's that?
It's what I call
a "get out of jail free" card.
If you win,
you don't need to explain anything.
Y'all gonna wanna see this.
Come on, uncuff me.
And if you lose...
there's nothing to explain.
What Barry had was a picture of Escobar
Don't you think the workers
will choke with all that smoke?
The pictures I took that day
helped to ID guys for months to come.
I like that.
loading cocaine on a tarmac
in Nicaragua. Why does that matter?
- Hitler said it.
- Fuck off.
There was Carlos Lehder...
Yes.
'Cause at the time, Nicaragua was
governed by the communist Sandinistas,
He also said that no politician
Let's build them a chimney.
should ever let his picture be taken
in a bathing suit.
who were letting Escobar
use their country as a landing strip
...the Ochoa brothers...
for cocaine shipments to the US.
There you go.
Colombian cocaine coming through
a communist country and into America?
I couldn't have made that up.
Gentlemen, the first three?
Fernando Galeano,
"the Wolfman"...
- Holy shit.
- It was too good.
If this business makes so much money,
why are you sending me coach?
- Gotta turn this over to the ambassador.
- Wait, wait, wait. No.
We just started up.
We have to be careful with money.
This leaks wide and Barry Seal
is a dead man. We gotta be careful.
- Don't be a dick.
- No, no, don't give me that dumb shit.
Why are you trying to protect some scumbag
who's trafficked over 500 tons?
- Come on.
- How much can a first class ticket cost?
I have a code of ethics
when it comes to informants.
Is that Gacha?
Well, that's what he said.
I don't know.
Why don't you buy it yourself?
But not when it comes
to torturing suspects with hot coffee.
I've never seen him
with other traffickers.
And if I tell you, Carlos...
- You know, I wouldn't judge Carrillo.
- Why is that?
Like her son, Pablo's mother
Hermilda was very resourceful.
And last but not least...
Gustavo and Pablo.
You had a partner killed.
He's had a dozen.
that what I want, sincerely...
Hey, Mom,
how much do you think we can fit in there?
Get pictures of that fucker.
is to help the poor people
of this country...
- Around five kilos, honey.
- That much?
do you believe me or what?
Trust me, Pablito.
I love it. Let's do it.
They were all under one roof
and Peña got us there to document it all.
Pablo held most of his campaign rallies
I always admired
Peña's commitment to informants,
in the poorest neighborhoods
of his electoral district.
but frankly,
Barry Seal wasn't an informant.
- Pablo.
- Thank you, my love.
He was just another busted trafficker
He placed himself on the side
of the poor and the weak
who ratted on the guys
he worked with... a snitch.
in the fight against the oligarchs,
"The Men of Always."
It's Gustavo.
What we didn't know was
that we were witnessing the formation
Five kilos, right?
of the famed Medellín cartel.
If I could use
the narco-communist connection
Pablo loved his young bride Tata,
and she loved him.
And just like any politician,
he made plenty of promises.
Pablo took advantage
of the kidnapping of Marta Ochoa
to get the resources we needed,
then fuck him.
He was a family man till the end.
to bring all the narcos together
for the very first time.
Only difference was Pablo had the men
and the money to back them up.
Strange bedfellows, indeed.
The guy they got to wear the jacket
was the Lion.
You have single-handedly
exposed a narco-communist connection.
- Meet my friend.
- Hello, how are you doing?
And then he proclaimed himself
their leader.
Hey, Pablo, this is Lion.
It was becoming clear to everyone
that Pablo was gonna win.
Washington is gonna go crazy.
He was a friend of Gustavo's who'd
spent his childhood in the United States.
What I propose at this moment, gentlemen,
Pablo! Pablo!
Thank you, Ambassador.
Says he wants to fly first class.
It's not like we're rich, right?
The only question remaining was...
what to do about that.
is that we form an organization.
This has to be highly classified
for the safety of the informant.
Pablo Escobar Gaviria.
How are you?
- Lion.
- Pleased to meet you, Lion.
Gustavo made good on his promise
to quit the labs,
Of course.
Here's three.
Pool our resources to train soldiers,
trade knowledge and buy information.
We're going to need two more,
right, Mom?
so Pablo put Carlos Lehder in charge.
Thank you.
- That's right.
- Pablito...
With characteristic German efficiency,
he turned the labs into Nazilandia,
In Washington, "highly classified"
didn't carry much water.
make sure it is not you
who wears it, OK?
And so the message is clear,
we're going to name our group
Look, my love...
it won't fit me.
and production rose 12 percent
in just two short months.
Especially when a Marine colonel named
Oliver North got his hands on the picture.
Try it on.
"Death to Kidnappers."
Come here.
I know every American parent
concerned about the drug problem
That's it.
Gacha and the Ochoas
adopted a wait-and-see attitude,
Good, right?
What I propose:
will be outraged to learn that
top Nicaraguan government officials
I will manage all operational aspects.
debating how and when
Pablo would dispose of Jairo Ortega,
One...
are deeply involved in drug trafficking.
his front man,
once the election was over.
- two...
- Wow, it holds a lot!
All you need to do
is cover my expenses.
As soon as the results
come out, Jairo Ortega will resign.
This picture shows Federico Vaughan,
...three.
What you gentlemen will receive in return:
two things.
a top aide to one of the nine comandantes
who rule Nicaragua,
- Two more.
- Got it. I'll be right back.
I say he's running toward his death.
He looks really handsome,
doesn't he?
One... I promise to end the kidnapping.
loading an aircraft with illegal narcotics
bound for the United States.
Listen, Lion,
that jacket fits you very nicely.
Yeah. Excuse me, ma'am, can you adjust
the jacket a little bit here in the back?
Two... and at this moment,
the most important...
As for us, we were kind of divided.
No, there seems to be no crime
to which the Sandinistas will not stoop.
- Aah!
- Listen to this guy.
He looks very handsome, son.
I promise to return
Marta Ochoa to her family.
We cannot have Colombia
become a narco state.
Being a rat is a dangerous business,
Like a fag model, isn't that right?
We need to find someone
who can prove this guy is a drug dealer.
Salud.
and Escobar's reach was long.
The Lion was one of the first guys
to ever bring coke into Miami.
Death to Kidnappers!
Let's stop his campaign before it starts.
No one will go on record.
Barry Seal refused federal protection...
I got a better idea.
...and met his end
in a parking lot in Baton Rouge.
Welcome to the United States.
We let him win.
Thank you.
Have a great day.
If we put him in the spotlight
and prove he's a trafficker,
Whoops.
We knew the meeting was over
when the hookers came to play.
Next, please.
the embarrassment alone
might get this country off its ass.
His contact was a crazy nut job
named Carlos Lehder,
Peña had finally
gotten one of his informants
half Colombian, half German,
and 100 percent playboy.
right into the heart of the action.
But first, we had to get proof
that Pablo was the drug dealer
we knew he was.
Motherfucker!
I told you we had to be careful.
Come in! Enjoy! Ooh!
- You got Barry Seal killed.
- Peña, if he wanted a long life,
Big fan of John Lennon and Adolf Hitler.
So we went to Suárez,
Don't forget La Quica!
Take care of him, too.
and gave him a lot of money.
- he should've worked at Kodak.
- You're responsible for his death.
Go figure.
Back in '79, this piece of work
was flying bales of grass up from Colombia
First, he told us that Pablo
was arrested for trafficking back in '76,
I didn't kill him, Escobar did.
on a fleet of small planes.
Sit down, my love.
and then he gave us the name
of a sergeant who could give us the files.
Now we can go after that motherfucker.
- What's up?
- What's up, son?
Look on the bright side, man.
- Welcome.
- Thanks a lot. How are ya?
- Everything good?
- Everything's good.
- How are you?
- Good. And you?
From then on, according to Reagan,
Whoo! It's so hot.
I like your hat.
Problem was, Suárez was on both the DEA
and the narcos' payroll.
fighting the narcos
was the same as fighting the commies.
What the hell are you doing
with a jacket on?
It looks good on you.
You like my jacket, brother?
We got a tidal wave of money
and all the resources we needed.
I got it in Colombia and look,
it has a little gift.
- Do you think so?
- Yes, it looks good.
Let's see.
Very cute.
The US Southern Command in Panama
sent us a care package:
I was in jail for a while, remember?
planes, helicopters,
you fucking name it. Everything.
- Sixty-six.
- Bullshit. I shot him first.
I saw this shit there.
It's pure poison.
What you got there
is the perfect product.
She should be here by now.
Pablo says the gringos
will fall in love with this shit.
Then Suárez gave us
the name of the journalist
Our resources and intel helped the
Colombians raid labs all over the country
You think she slipped?
who reported the arrest...
It's gonna fuck up their brains,
that's for sure.
Nah, she's no dummy.
...and then the lawyer
who defended Pablo...
and burn 'em straight to the ground,
seizing over a billion dollars in coke.
Yes, sir.
and finally, the judge
who signed Pablo's arrest warrant.
Maybe she's getting pretty for you.
We were kicking ass,
and the narcos were feeling it.
Here you go.
Yeah.
We were like the Bermuda Triangle.
Go on. There are five kilos.
The price of cocaine in Miami
was skyrocketing.
You get too close to us,
you disappear.
Where are you going?
Despite all this, we'd yet
to net one of the Medellín kingpins...
I'm gonna get another jacket,
brother.
We gotta get something
on this motherfucker.
We'll meet at the same time tomorrow,
all right?
If he was arrested,
there's gotta be a mug shot.
till we put a tracking device
on a Colombian-bound shipment of ether,
Yeah, well, the file's gone.
The Lion made more than 20 flights
between Medellín and Miami.
If there was a mug shot,
then it's gone, too.
the essential ingredient
in cocaine processing.
Aah...
Got it!
Drugs in, cash out.
If there was a photo,
there's a negative.
The barrel that we tracked
brought us to Tranquilandia,
And the rich and famous in Miami
snorted every single gram of it.
Helena wanted a US visa so bad,
Finally, it dawned on us.
Medellín's biggest processing lab,
and we hit it hard.
she was willing to do anything
to help our cause.
And in no time,
Pablo had to replace his cars with trucks.
We had to find someone
without Suárez's help,
The ensuing gun battle
cost dozens of men...
And that was a problem.
and that was the photographer
who had taken Pablo's mug shot years ago.
Gustavo had the trucks
filled to the brim with potatoes,
- You're tired.
- Hm?
but in the end,
it got us our biggest victory to date,
the major item
Colombia imported from Peru.
the first of the Medellín kingpins:
Carlos Lehder.
Let me relax you a bit.
He didn't even have to bribe the cops.
In my tent is a bag with $50,000...
We got his negatives, and for safekeeping,
we put him into witness protection.
The coke paste
was hidden in the spare tires.
ten times this if you give me one hour.
Each tire could fit about 20 kilos.
So what happened at that meeting
that made you so tired?
There's no way out,
Carlitos. You're going to Disneyland.
Ten trucks, 20 kilos each,
going back and forth every day...
- How long have you had this picture?
- That's classified.
You do the math.
No way the Lion could transport it all.
And what am I doing here?
Lehder was immediately
extradited to the States,
What did you hear?
It's not America's role to get involved
in other countries' elections.
Pretty soon,
the Lion had to come up with new ways
Nothing.
Just making conversation.
Once again, the hand
of the United States remains invisible.
where a federal court
sentenced him to life... plus 135 years.
to smuggle the drug to Miami.
The briefcase doesn't have a false bottom?
Your party took money from Escobar.
I should think
you'd want to get ahead of this.
Extradition worked.
Carlos will die in an American jail.
You guys are pilots,
Everyone took money.
By the way, it's all American money,
so why don't you take this to the press?
so you can get this stuff by
without a problem.
They're
telling me the girl left a long time ago.
And no one savored this victory
more than the Colombians.
It should come from you.
You're the Minister of Justice.
Look, it's $150,000 per kilo,
so whatever you want.
- She's already dead.
- No, they wouldn't kill her at the hotel.
For anti-narco candidate
Luis Carlos Galán,
Then they killed her somewhere else.
She knew the risks.
Come election day,
sure enough, it was a landslide.
it would provide him the momentum
he needed to propel him to the presidency.
We'll take four.
If we're going back,
we go back now.
All right, much better.
The New Liberal party had the candidate
Take these two and tell Jairo
to give you two more. All right?
who got the most votes
in all of Antioquia...
Extradition would become his battle cry.
I want you to find the girl.
Gentlemen?
and his name was Jairo Ortega.
- All right.
- Perfect. Thank you very much.
I can pick up a sicario.
You OK with that?
Ladies and gentlemen,
Thank you.
- See you later.
- Later.
- I'm going with you.
- What about Fresh Meat?
with clear use of my
mental and physical faculties...
And for the narcos,
this was a declaration of war.
Gonna stick around here
and see if she shows up, OK?
Come in, please.
- Yeah, and where are you going?
- We're gonna go look for her.
I wish to communicate to you my decision
What happened to Carlos was terrible.
That's it, guys.
to resign from my seat
in the Congress of the Republic...
Look, here are the packets.
But I have already presented a motion
before the Supreme Court of Colombia
...for reasons of family and health.
You take a packet...
you dip it in the oil and swallow it.
against the legality of extradition.
But I am completely certain that
my friend Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria
Easy, right?
They are examining it this week
at the Palace of Justice.
You swallow 50,
and I pay you $10,000.
All right?
is going to continue
our social and political ideas,
But with you two,
we have a problem.
Can we buy someone in that court?
You girls are pregnant, right?
- Guys.
- Hey, what happened?
because Pablo is the voice of the people.
That's good, because US Customs
won't search pregnant women.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you very much, Jairo.
Unfortunately, no.
That little girl doesn't move.
Like a dead cow.
It's the only institution in this country
that is incorruptible.
I will give my best effort.
You two can easily swallow 70
instead of 50.
What, did you kill her?
Thank you very much.
Let's pray that the ruling
comes out in our favor.
And I'll pay you $15,000
to help you with the kids.
Brother... even after he's dead,
All right? All right. Perfect.
Carlos still has a sentence
of 135 years in prison.
It's my turn now.
During the early '80s,
most flights out of Bogotá
He's totally fucked.
This is gringo bullshit.
had several mules on them.
That happened to him for speaking
about the revolution on the radio.
They didn't even know about each other.
And you know what?
We're next, aren't we?
Getting in was easy, because nobody
worried about cocaine in America.
You're right.
Pablito?
All we cared about was grass.
Do you have an answer or what?
Pretty soon, cocaine was hidden in
almost every legitimate Colombian export.
Where's the girl?
Well... in my opinion, a jail
in the United States is worse than death.
- Where's the girl, asshole?
- I don't know.
Fish, coffee, flowers, rubber hoses...
anything.
Imagine you were born in a poor family,
I don't know.
in a poor city, in a poor country,
We can never forget
what happened to Carlos.
Choke him.
and by the time you were 28 years old,
Carlos was one of us.
you have so much money
you can't even count it.
Fabio is right.
The Americans are fucking us.
Enough with the party.
What do you do?
You make your dreams come true.
But remember,
there's something they want more than us.
So, brothers...
But even that didn't do it.
I gotta rough this girl up.
The real game changer was filling
Lehder's planes with coke instead of weed.
Gacha wants to know
if she knows something.
it's time to give them what they want,
isn't it?
Gacha's paranoid.
I didn't think our paths
would cross again.
Problem is, nobody can control
the dreams they have.
Wait a second...
I don't like them bruised.
What you want isn't going to be easy.
It's very risky.
Do you trust this guy?
I don't know.
He was in prison in the United States.
Let me have a little more fun,
then I'll let her go.
It's going to require weapons and men.
There will be casualties.
Especially if you were Pablo Escobar.
- So is he gay or what?
- Oh, for sure he's gay.
It's all right, boys.
I understand what you want.
How much are we talking about?
But he's got good routes.
This one's for all of you!
Slap her around!
Especially if you grew up in Colombia.
Two million US dollars.
- Amigos!
- Hello, Carlos.
Gustavo Gaviria,
nice to meet you.
There's a reason magical realism
was born in Colombia.
It's very dangerous.
- Nice to meet you.
- My cousin.
Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria.
Nice to meet you.
Fighting a revolution
comes with sacrifice...
- Cousin? Nice to meet you.
- How was your flight?
It's a country where
dreams and reality are conflated...
Smooth.
and it goes without saying
that it will dangerous, right?
Let's get down to business.
The Lion tells us you've been transporting
a lot of marijuana in your plane.
Any news on the radio?
where, in their heads,
people fly as high as Icarus.
- Should I tell him?
- No. Remember what Carrillo said.
- That's true.
- About how much per flight?
Sorry, I don't speak English.
But even magical realism has its limits.
- How far?
- Miami.
Congressman Escobar... Sir!
Excuse me.
But for us, brother...
- Somewhere around 1000 kilos.
- 1000 kilos?
Allow me to remind you
of the norms of etiquette.
it is our duty to fight to the very end.
Counting the gasoline.
You cannot enter the hall
if you don't have a tie.
- How far is it?
- Come on, you piece of shit.
We have an historical obligation.
All right.
- What is your name?
- Juan.
Look, Juan...
We can't forget that.
Carlos...
I'm his girlfriend.
Yes?
that is a really nice tie.
- My girlfriend gave it to me.
- Really?
Yes.
What if we take out the seats,
the carpet and all the other crap
Well, she's in the history books now.
and only leave space for the pilot?
Can you fit more?
Meet Pablo Escobar.
- Thank you very much, my son.
- Thank you, sir.
We'll leave the engine, right?
- Thank you.
- All right.
Miss.
- OK.
- We have a deal.
How much more?
All right, then.
About... 300 more.
And when you get too close to the sun...
We were just leaving.
All right then, Mr. Carlos.
Let's take a walk.
your dreams may melt away.
Good night.
Within months after meeting Cockroach,
Pablo was establishing the first dedicated
narco routes from Colombia to America.
What the hell is this?
Why are you meeting with Escobar?
We made a deal...
obviously for money.
It was a real milestone
in the story of narcotics, folks.
Good morning.
Then Pablo closed The Kitchen
and started opening cocaine labs
This is to inform you that we have
a quorum and may now begin our session.
In exchange for what?
Unless you are willing to be part of it,
I cannot say.
in the middle of the jungle.
The Minister of Justice,
Rodrigo Lara Bonilla,
Under the canopy cover
of the Colombian rainforest,
Helena?
It's a partnership,
necessary for the revolutionary fight.
he could expand his production capability
indefinitely without anybody noticing it.
is present here today
to address this honorable Congress.
I fight for the people...
not for drug traffickers.
I'm going to get you
out of here, OK? I promise.
I give the floor to you, Mr. Minister.
Thank you very much.
We brought you a little present.
Brazilians.
Much has been made
of the issue of drug money,
Best asses in the world,
believe me.
No, I'm not feeling well.
"hot money,"
in our national political process.
- What's up, Cuca?
- Hello.
Connie?
Hey, Gustavo.
All right. She's coming out.
I myself have been accused
of receiving campaign contributions
Elisa? What's going on?
What the fuck is up with you guys?
- I need to talk to you.
- About what?
You're flying around in planes...
from the narcotics traffickers
who have bought influence in these halls.
You told me your husband
works at the embassy.
Yeah.
- while I'm rotting here in this jungle?
- Look, Cuca--
I need you to speak with him
and warn him.
Copy, Major.
About what?
Look, let us explain what we have to--
Let's go, boys.
Pablo Escobar is planning something
with a communist group called the M-19.
Wait.
Hey, gringo.
Carrillo is calling. Come on.
From now on,
in all of my labs...
To this charge, I plead guilty.
I don't know what it is,
but I know it's gonna be bad.
I'll build a large house
with air-conditioning, with a pool...
No habla inglés, huh?
Wait, Pablo Escobar?
How do you know anything about Escobar?
In my eyes,
the sin of turning a blind eye
¡Vamos!
I... I just know.
You need to warn him...
- And whores from Brazil.
- ...and whores from Brazil.
is as great as the sin
of outright corruption.
and you need to hide me.
- Just for you.
- One problem.
We are a nation of the blind,
and in our blindness,
OK. Come on.
These are my labs. Mm?
Where the fuck's Peña?
¿Dónde está Peña?
we have sold our country
to the highest bidder.
Over there.
Steve's already at work,
but Javi lives downstairs.
It's time for us to open our eyes
and to see the light.
Relax.
No one's arguing with you.
Come show me the production
and we'll talk later.
I just hope he's here.
Pablo couldn't hide his success
from his friends.
Congressman Escobar...
I am.
They were violent, crazy and filthy rich.
you stated that your great fortune
was built from a taxi company.
- Well, what have we here?
- I'll explain later.
- How is she?
- Sedated.
I'll be right back. Go.
Guys used to getting what they want,
one way or another.
How something like this
can make so much money!
- Is she gonna be OK?
- Physically, yeah.
This photograph
clearly contradicts your claim.
- She told me that Escobar...
- Slow down.
Now I ask myself...
if I should get involved with this.
Mentally, I haven't got a fucking clue.
For this reason,
I demand your resignation.
...hired guerrillas called M-19. Thinks
they're gonna do something terrible.
- You left me behind on purpose.
- Look, man--
You are not welcome in this chamber.
- Slow down.
- Escobar is using members of M-19.
What do you think, Pablo?
If we're gonna be partners,
I don't get left behind.
I heard the "potato" business
is like the "egg" business.
You don't belong here.
- Say that again?
- Pablo Escobar and M-19 guerrillas.
I didn't come all the way down here, Peña,
to sit on the fucking sidelines.
Escobar and M-19?
I wouldn't get involved.
She didn't tell me any details,
just that it would be bad.
Look, man,
I took a good look at the market.
No... that doesn't make any sense.
Importing potatoes from Peru is easy.
Whatever's going on here...
I'm in all the way.
She asked me to hide her,
so I took her to Javi's apartment.
- Of course. Same old contraband routes.
- Mm.
OK. All right.
Be careful, guys. If we all start
buying potatoes at the same time,
Is that understood?
the Peruvians will raise the price.
Understood.
They also grow potatoes in Bolivia.
We can reduce the cost of
the refining process if we buy together.
I hope you know what that means.
- Agent Murphy!
- All right.
Ambassador, I got information
with Escobar and M-19. I think they're...
Well, guys, the hard part
is getting the merchandise to Miami.
- ...supreme court building.
- Oh, my God.
You need a lot of creativity for that.
"Oh, my God" is right.
Financed by Escobar, the M-19 guerrillas
stormed the Palace of Justice
Pablo's message
to the kidnappers was simple.
How much would you charge us
to be "creative"?
He was going to kill them, one by one,
until he got Marta Ochoa back.
and occupied the supreme court.
You deliver the product to me, labeled.
They took over 100 hostages
and made a bunch of demands
Ivan "the Terrible" thought he could
hide in the jungle and wait it out.
about the redistribution of wealth
and an end to injustice and tyranny...
I will take it to Miami
and deliver it to your contact there.
Sooner or later,
he figured the narcos would cave in.
Thank you very much, Juan.
Very kind.
but it was all bullshit.
Better yet, Lehder will do it.
What interests the narcos
I'll charge 35 percent of the sales value,
Big mistake.
isn't just the fall
of the Minister of Justice,
The military attacked.
Dozens of lives
were lost in the carnage,
M-19 didn't stand a chance.
but I'll insure the safety of your load
up to 50 percent of the value.
but also to impede the strategy of
the government to combat his interests.
including half of
Colombia's supreme court justices.
The potato business is ours.
We don't need--
His two arms: silver or lead.
Most of the M-19 were killed.
Some escaped... but not before
accomplishing their true goal:
Deal?
I want to inform the people
that the Minister of Justice has 24 hours
"Deliver Marta Ochoa
safe and sound... or your family is next."
Deal.
setting fire to the room that contained
600,000 pages of evidence against Escobar.
Sounds good to me.
within which to present concrete proof
regarding the insinuations he made
All right,
I will create my own routes
Signed, "Death to Kidnappers."
the day before yesterday
in the Hall of Representatives.
The entire case against him
turned to ash.
and stop using your services
as soon as possible. OK?
To the contrary,
I will proceed to denounce him legally
We expect nothing less, Gonzalo.
Please! Please, let me go.
before the authorities
and before the Colombian justice system.
In the United States,
the Mafia makes witnesses disappear
Partners?
- Hurry up!
- Please, don't!
Needless to say,
Marta Ochoa was released unharmed.
Pablo and his lawyers went on the offense,
so they can't testify in court.
trying to smear Lara with accusations.
We know your policy toward partners.
In Colombia, Pablo Escobar
made the whole court disappear.
I am not looking
for, nor do I long for a confrontation
Let's just call us...
before the Colombian people.
"friendly associates."
I look for peace,
I have always preached peace,
The fires set by guerrillas
earlier in the day grew even stronger
To Miami.
And the killing didn't stop.
and have longed for peace and
the prosperity of the Colombian people.
as cannon shells exploded inside.
To Miami!
Pablo had tasted blood,
and he liked it.
It's important to realize
that when members of Congress
Tell him to get a little closer.
can be threatened or bought at will,
A little closer. A little closer!
we see with clarity the real dimension
of the drug problem here in Colombia.
- Where is she?
- Well, come on in.
You know what, boss?
Go a little higher.
You, up! Who in the fuck is she
and why is the military after her?
When I started, a one-kilo
grass bust was cause for celebration.
A little bit higher
and a little bit closer
But Lara wouldn't back down.
Put the gun away.
so you can see the tree!
He denounced narcos at every opportunity,
Put it away.
going after the guys
that we hadn't been able to touch.
That's it.
She told me who she is.
Put the gun away.
He revealed that six
of the country's nine soccer teams
- Can I say something?
- No, you may not.
Now a little bit higher
so you can see the little tree!
And before long,
we were seizing 60 kilos of coke a day.
were owned by drug traffickers.
Murphy... calm down.
That...
Gacha the Mexican was forced
to give up ownership of his team,
I have no idea
why you'd get yourself involved in this.
That's it. Perfect.
We thought we were
making a huge difference.
DEATH TO KIDNAPPERS
Your wife brought her to me.
A little more.
aptly nicknamed "The Millionaires."
That's it! There you go.
Lara denied flying permits
for 57 planes in the Ochoa fleet.
I appreciate you putting yourself
out there for my wife, I truly do,
but why are we risking
our whole careers over this woman?
Truth is,
we weren't even making a dent.
- Much better.
- Yes, boss.
Because she can prove
that Pablo was behind the palace siege.
They let us have 60
so they could bring in 600.
He even fined Pablo
for illegal importation
of elephants and camels from Africa.
If she can tie Escobar to the siege,
I say we bring her in.
Didn't I tell you
not to let anyone into the park?
Well, she's M-19.
And with the action of one brave man,
Noonan would have to turn her over
to the Colombian military
- I'll take care of it.
- Are you crazy or what?
Pablo knew his dream
of presidency was over.
and then she gets disappeared.
Stupid asshole.
I'd like to avoid
another Barry Seal situation.
Pablo's coke flooded in.
It's a woman with a baby.
What are required are honest men,
So we're gonna
harbor a communist fugitive?
It didn't take long
for Miami to get addicted.
Take a picture
so we can send it to the newspapers.
men who are able to put themselves
up against drug traffickers,
Look, all she did was warn us.
And I mean that.
She's not on anybody's radar.
who with complete tranquility buy or kill
any person or government institution
It was like the whole city was
running around trying to get this shit.
Do it.
Good day, ma'am.
She's not involved in anything.
- Good day.
- I'm sorry, but the park is closed today.
And with the money...
who is against their interests.
The red X's you see in these pictures
indicate M-19 revolutionaries
came the violence.
What do you mean the park is closed?
Rodrigo Lara became the most
important political figure in Colombia
May I escort you out?
terminated by
the Colombian Special Forces.
The hippies had been
replaced by Colombians,
Why is it closed?
I come by here every day.
with his stand against the narcos.
and these guys didn't wear flip-flops.
It's because there is a foul odor
and I don't want the child to get sick.
He just wouldn't stop going after them.
The remaining individuals you see
are fugitives.
His bravery in the face of danger made him
the most wanted man in the country.
Folks, this is more complicated
than what it seems.
I thought I smelled something.
This was Escobar, classic.
He's cut a deal with M-19.
- Right?
- Yes.
For his own safety, he was appointed
Colombian ambassador to Czechoslovakia.
Oh, look,
what a beautiful little baby.
Right, just like his dad.
Thank you very much.
Next you'll tell us
Escobar sank the Titanic.
He was slated to leave in two weeks,
but a lot could happen in two weeks.
- You must be proud.
- Yes, of course.
Was it coincidence the extradition
evidence against him was destroyed?
My wife and I
are having a baby very soon.
He doesn't hold grudges,
not if it suits his purposes.
I think it might be a good idea
for you to wear this until you leave.
Oh, very good.
Congratulations!
- How do you know he cut a deal?
- We have a confidential informant.
I don't know if it's a boy or a girl,
but as long as it's healthy.
You feel responsible, is that it?
You willing to identify this informant,
Agent Peña?
Yes, of course.
The most important thing is health.
The Miami coroner
said Colombians were like Dixie cups.
Somewhat, yes, sir.
- No, I am not.
- Needless to say...
Are you so arrogant to think
you had any influence over my actions?
Southern Command has rescinded
its offer of resources to the DEA
Use 'em once,
then throw 'em away.
Sending the photos
of the hanging M-19 to the newspapers
That I put my life
and the life of my family at risk
in light of this communist aggression.
The Dade County morgue couldn't
fit all the bodies from the drug war.
gave Pablo an image of invincibility.
We need to target the M-19 leadership:
for American policy objectives?
Ivan "the Terrible" Torres
and Elisa Alvarez.
They had to rent a refrigerated truck
from a local company
If he could do this
to the feared communists,
he could do it to anyone.
Let me assure you, Agent Murphy,
outside of providing me with the picture,
to hold all the extra corpses.
Ivan "the Terrible"
was quick to realize...
you... did nothing.
That was the first person I ever shot.
there was only one thing he could do.
The decision to speak out
was solely mine.
A teenager not old enough
to buy a six-pack.
And I highly advise you
to wear this vest, sir.
Hey, Don Pablo.
What do you want us to do
with this guy?
Should I kill him or what?
They're looking for us everywhere.
I will accept this vest... out of respect
for your concern with my well-being.
What did you expect?
That it would be any different?
From what I can see,
you're not going to stop.
But I would advise you one thing
while you remain in Colombia.
Hey... it was self-defense.
You did a very good job.
Here I am,
so you can finish what you started...
And what is that?
- Kevin called you?
- He's worried about you.
We accept your help,
but never your condescension.
but with the sword of Bolívar.
Did he forget to tell you
the kid was 17?
When all this is over, Colombians
will be the heroes, and the victims.
He sells drugs, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, then fuck him.
John Wayne only exists in Hollywood.
Just wear the vest.
You can't imagine how much
this is going to help our cause.
No, brother.
The truth is, you helped mine.
What happened?
- Coming through!
- I was about to finish my shift
You, Ivan...
when we got hit
with the lights and sirens.
gave me the sword of Simón Bolívar.
Stay with me.
Oh, Pablito.
I have an unconscious pregnant female.
We knew they wouldn't
accept you in that circle.
Paramedics said she collapsed
after she got off her flight.
It's a very beautiful gift.
Thank you very much.
The same one that freed this country.
By the time she got to us,
she was barely breathing.
Damned bastards.
- Pressure 60 over 40.
- Dilated pupils, rapid pulse.
Stand up.
Now it belongs to you.
I knew she'd overdosed on cocaine...
...but she had no residue on her nostrils,
no injection marks.
I guarantee no harm
will come to you or your family.
You're too good for them, Pablito.
With it, you will continue the fight...
to free this country.
We did everything we could.
She died in the ER.
From now on,
we are going to work together.
I promise you,
I will continue the fight.
We tried to save the baby...
You earned it, brother.
As for me...
I'll be in Panama until this blows over.
The baby died in my hands.
Go in peace, brother.
We are also...
I'm so sorry.
This is a fight
that you cannot win, cousin.
She was body-packing
11 ounces of cocaine.
Make sure you grab the briefcase.
You need to think more
about your family and the business...
Two of the pellets split open.
And the fucking sword.
Twelve grams in her bloodstream.
and abandon that ridiculousness
once and for all.
Is that what I think it is?
No one survives that.
You've gotta be kidding.
I will fix it.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.MY-SUBS.com
I want you
to run my day-to-day operations.
Why won't Pablo ever see me?
I spent all this time
waiting around for him.
And you'll do what?
Due to the vicious lies
and slander cast my way
Tell me something, Cockroach.
Liberate Colombia.
Did you ever think
you were going to have this much money?
by Minister Lara and his cronies,
Fuck the money.
I'm talking renegotiation.
I've decided to announce my resignation
from Congress of the Republic.
If it wasn't for me, you two
would still be smuggling cigarettes.
Welcome to the Medellín cartel.
I ran as a representative
for the common man,
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Never say that to Pablo.
a voice for those who had no voice,
He's not as forgiving as I am.
but that has happened
through much of our history.
The powerful have conspired to silence me.
Pablo was fucking Cockroach over.
I dreamt of doing good.
But Cockroach
should've listened to Gustavo.
The narcos had their army,
but me and Peña had ours, too.
Those dreams are over.
Instead, he found another way
to get his fair share.
Many Colombians
like Major Horacio Carrillo
But make no mistake...
I will not go quietly.
were so invested
in the future of their country
Stop!
that they were ready
to do whatever it took to fix it.
I will fight.
"The Men of Always" are mistaken
This was a war that would shake
an entire country to its foundations.
if they think they can defeat
Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria!
And in the carnage...
mine would be shaken as well.
What do you have in the spare tires?
Even my wife, Connie,
wanted to help.
390 kilos, Pablo.
We lost it.
She got a job as a nurse
in a local comuna.
Thank you very much.
Gustavo, what do you mean
"we lost it"?
She wanted to make a difference.
Thank you very much.
Just what I said, we lost it.
I guess she forgot we were in Colombia.
Look, our escolta will drive me
there and back every day.
We lost it? It just disappeared?
Into thin air or what?
- Yeah.
- He'll wait outside all day.
Don't mess with me, Pablo.
We lost it.
You know the last time you were in church
is when we got married.
It looks like the cops must have stopped
the guys when they were leaving Ipsalia.
Well, I'm letting the Lord
back into my life.
Hey, stop right here.
Look...
we've paid every cop
from here to Ipsalia.
Praise God.
He didn't wear it.
So how did we lose a load, brother?
It looks like Colonel Herrera
suddenly turned honest.
Wouldn't have made a difference.
Know what I mean?
Our strategy had gotten a good man killed.
Perdón.
It was the first time
I'd felt guilty about my job.
And how much is he asking?
I want that escolta watching
every inch of you at that comuna now.
Too much.
Hey, did we leave the door open?
- As for Suárez...
- Hey.
...he made so much money
playing both sides,
What are you going to do?
Oh, my God, Steve!
he decided to lift our spirits by giving
the DEA a token of his appreciation.
Come back, Pablo.
Get back.
Don't go and risk it for this asshole.
Come back.
I brought this for your friend's wife.
Where are you going, Pablo?
Pablo?
- I hope she likes it.
- No, gracias.
You stay right there
and don't move.
You're fucking crazy, asshole.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.MY-SUBS.com
What's going on, brother?
Mr. Escobar...
- we need to renegotiate.
- Eat shit.
Eat. Shit.
What if I shot you in the head?
Are you sure about this, Colonel?
He hasn't stopped laughing
since we arrested him.
We're DAS, Ibarra.
What's that faggot gonna do?
There we are.
No, lower, lower.
No that low.
Ready.
Another one, another one.
I'm ready.
Pablo didn't know it then...
...but this mug shot was gonna cause him
a lot of grief down the line.
Remove the handcuffs.
You can go now, officer.
Sit down, Mr. Pablo.
We counted more than 300 kilos
in those trucks.
That's a street value
of over four million dollars, Mr. Escobar.
And you only gave us $150,000.
Well, that's what we agreed upon.
You know something?
I make deals for a living.
Now you can either accept my deal
or accept the consequences. You decide.
Or we can renegotiate,
come to an agreement,
and everyone goes home happy.
Deal?
I'll give you one million dollars...
under one condition.
What is it?
Someone in my organization
gave you the street value of my cocaine.
Otherwise, how would you know?
Give me a name...
and you won't have
to split the cash with him.
Turns out Cockroach was a real cockroach.
Not only did he sell Pablo
to the authorities,
he was stealing from him all along
and selling his coke in Miami, too.
Cockroach's dealer was Germán Zapata,
a Colombian with a plumbing business
that served as a front
for his cocaine operation.
He had 1200 keys in the van...
and guess who was buying the load?
The plan was to trade vehicles,
and Zapata would be arrested
once he left the port.
1200 kilos.
That would get us
on the cover of the Miami Herald.
OK, gringos.
How's the plumbing business?
Fine.
- How's it look?
- Plumbing business is very good.
Come on, amigo.
I'll show you.
Everything was going perfect.
Like I said, amigo...
100 percent pure.
Except that Pablo was onto Cockroach.
Got a full load here, Murph--
Don't move! Don't move.
Get down!
Hands! Down!
Don't look at me.
Fucking...
In the case of
the State of Florida v. Juan Diego Díaz,
after taking into account
all due considerations,
bail has been set at two million dollars,
or a bond of $200,000.
I got to the courthouse early
the day of La Quica's trial.
My testimony was gonna
put that bastard on death row.
The US District Attorney said La Quica
met his bail of two million dollars,
paid by a wire transfer from, well...
why don't you take a guess?
La Quica boarded
and was back in Medellín by midnight.
From '79 to '84,
there were 3,245 murders in Miami.
And outside the Tourist Bureau
and the cops,
no one much cared about that.
What got the US government
to take notice was the money.
Billions of dollars a year,
all flowing from the US to Colombia.
And that... America couldn't take.
A group of powerful businessmen
went and met with President Reagan.
They were terrified the narco economy
would sink the real economy of Miami.
Or... maybe they were pissed off
that they weren't getting a cut.
Whatever it was, the businessmen
came at just the right time.
It's back-to-school time
for America's children...
It was time for America
to suit up against a new enemy.
Drugs are menacing our society.
They're threatening our values
and undercutting our institutions.
They're killing our children.
It was classic Reagan.
Folksy, direct and tough.
He vowed to go after drugs
at the source.
But it was Nancy who stole the show.
So to my young friends out there,
life can be great.
But not when you can't see it.
So open your eyes to life, to see it
in the vivid colors that God gave us
as a precious gift to His children.
Say yes to your life.
And when it comes to drugs and alcohol...
just say no.
No, no, no!
No, Pablo, no, no!
No, no!
They say when a nuclear holocaust
destroys the world,
only the cockroaches will survive.
Leave that piece of shit there.
I guess they were wrong.
During his career,
Pablo would kill over a thousand cops.
But I wouldn't learn that till later.
My dad volunteered to fight
in World War II because of Pearl Harbor.
But you think he knew anybody in Hawaii?
No way.
He was a West Virginia farm boy,
but these fuckers stepped on our soil.
So he laced up his army boots
and went to fight.
It was his duty.
Cocaine in Miami?
Kilos from Colombia?
This was my war.
This was my duty.
And I was ready to fight it.
And my wife was ready
to fight it with me, too.
Your ticket, please.
OK.
We had no idea
what we were in for.
One year later... all that patriotic
bullshit was right out the window.
OK, man, what do we got?
- We got Poison...
- Excellent. Who else?
We got Lizard.
Uh...
We got, we got...
- Big Badmouth.
- That motherfucker.
- Thank you for the gift, agent.
- No problem.
If there's one thing
I've learned in the narco world,
it's that life is more complicated
than you think.
Good and bad...
they're relative concepts.
In the world of drug dealers,
you do what you think is right...
and hope for the best.
Look at what happened, boss.
They killed Poison at La Dispensaria.
- Who did it?
- I think it was Carrillo.
And there was a gringo DEA agent
taking pictures.
- Raise the bounty.
- On Carrillo, sir?
I'll pay half a million
for the head of a DEA agent.
Half a million?
Do it.
As you wish, sir.
Fucking gringos.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.MY-SUBS.com